<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="hello">Hello World, AdventuresofLillyActivity!</string>
    <string name="app_name">Adventures of Lilly</string>
	<string name="lilly_1_1">One sunny day in San Diego Lilly the dog awoke, sad and alone.  Lilly needed a friend.  Little did Lilly know, today would be the day she would not only meet a friend, but find a family.</string>
    <string name="lilly_1_2">That afternoon, two new people Lilly had never seen before came into her pen.  Lilly was scared of the strangers and tried to stay as far away as she could.  The strangers knelt down and offered Lilly treats!</string>
    <string name="lilly_1_3">Slowly Lilly came closer, surely the nice lady who fed her each day wouldn’t bring people to meet her if they weren’t friendly.</string>
    <string name="lilly_1_4">Lilly didn’t know it yet, but the two strangers were about to become her mommy and daddy.  Lilly’s first great adventure was about to begin!</string>
    <string name="lilly_1_5">Lilly’s new parents picked out a pretty pink collar and a leash with flowers on it.  Lilly watched as her mommy and daddy talked to the animal shelter workers and signed some papers. Then they waved good bye, Lilly was their puppy now!</string>
    <string name="lilly_1_6">Lilly was nervous as she and her new parents got in the car.  Lilly’s mommy held her close and patted her back on the way home.  Lilly began to relax as her mommy and daddy reassure her and gives her lots of hugs and pats.</string>
    <string name="lilly_1_7">There was only one problem. Lilly needed a name! Her parents went back and forth with suggestions, but nothing sounded quite.  Finally Lilly’s mom noticed the beautiful flowers on her leash.  This gave Lilly’s mom an idea… flower… hmmm my favorite flower is a Lilly! Yes! Lilly!  Lilly is her name! Daddy agreed. </string>
    <string name="lilly_1_8">Now Lilly had a mommy, a daddy and a name. she was a very happy puppy and couldn’t wait to explore her new home!</string>
                        
</resources>